LOVEMI
LOVEMI LOVEMI
KILL ME KILL ME
The music and the music.
I will admit my self.
The fear of fiction.
The truth and truth and truth.
I don't know what my life is.
I don't care about this song.
I won't say no high tension.
The role of the play is that.
I'm not a big fan.
Love me! Love me!
I'm not a fighter Love me! Hey!
Love me!
Love me! Love me!
Love
Nice to meet you, child of
Zenin, descendant of Michizane,
cursed womb death painting,
and vessel of Sukuna.
I guess you don't have a
greeting for me, Tengen.
So this thing...
This person... Person... It's Tengen?
It's not our first time
meeting, Yuki Sukumo.
Tell me why you closed
the Tombs of the Star.
I was wary of you being
aligned with Kenjaku.
I can't tell what's going on in
people's hearts, after all. Kenjaku?
What was once Noritoshi Kamo,
the sorcerer who's currently
inhabiting Suguru Gato's body.
A net of compassion and
a rope of salvation.
Wasn't even trying for sarcasm.
You look nothing like how
I pictured you, Tengen.
Ballsy to insert himself
into the conversation.
Just because I'm immortal
doesn't make me ageless.
You'd look like this too
if you were 500 years old.
Seriously?
My aging has sped up.
Ever since I failed to assimilate with
the Star Plasma vessel 12 years ago,
my identity as an individual has vanished.
Now you can consider my
existence as the world itself.
So there wasn't actually another
Star Plasma vessel back then.
That explains why there isn't a new voice.
Excuse me?
We came here to learn Kenjaku's goal,
and also to learn about how
to open the prison realm.
Could you tell us what you know about it?
Of course.
But I must impose one condition
first, and it's non-negotiable.
Yuta Okotsu, Yukitsukumo, and
the Cursed Womb Death Painting.
I'll need two of you three
to remain behind here.
Remain behind and guard me.
Guard you?
You said you're immortal.
Are you afraid of being
sealed or something?
That isn't fair.
Without telling us why or
how long we're guarding you.
In that case...
Let me speak of Kenjaku.
That man's objective is to force the
evolution of mankind throughout all of Japan.
I heard about that but how
does he actually intend
to do it and why didn't
Kenjaku use your barriers
back when he could to
turn everyone in Japan
into Jujutsu sorcerers
with idle transfiguration?
For a simple reason he lacked
the cursed energy to do so.
The cursed energy refined through
maelstrom can't return to the sorcerer.
Besides a curse technique evolving people
one at a time is far too inefficient.
So Kenjaku's new method of evolution
is to assimilate mankind with me.
But wait I thought
your assimilation should
only be possible with
the star plasma vessel?
Previously that was true but since
I started evolving 12 years ago,
assimilation with someone other than
the star plasma vessel is possible.
Even so you're only one person.
He still can't assimilate with
multiple people at once. Wrong.
Right now the image you are seeing
of me is not my actual self.
Now that I've evolved my soul
is everywhere all the time.
Like I said before the world
itself is who I am now.
People who assimilated with me would
become something more than a sorcerer.
They'd become a new creature that at the
same time is both there and not there.
It is because of my barrier
techniques that I was able
to retain my shape and reason
after I started evolving.
However, if mankind
were to begin evolving,
even if only one person
went out of control,
the world would end. Why?
There would be no boundaries
between individuals.
Evil would spread to all instantly.
The impurities of a hundred million
people would flood the world.
What happened in Tokyo would be
recreated on a worldwide scale.
What would make him want
to do something like that?
That, I do not know.
As I said, there's no telling
what's inside people's hearts.
If that's the case,
as long as you reject the
assimilation, won't everything be fine?
Now we're getting to why I need guarding.
Since I have evolved,
my nature is closer to that of a cursed
spirit than it is to that of a human being.
So I can be targeted by
cursed spirit manipulation.
Considering Kenjaku's enormous
strength as a sorcerer,
I would likely be absorbed the
moment he made contact with me.
That's why my main body is rejecting
everything in the tombs of the star right now.
That's why you need guarding?
Correct.
Kenjaku is second only to me in
his skill with barrier techniques.
I don't know when he'll manage to break
the seal on the tombs of the star.
Why is this happening now?
The star plasma vessel
assimilation failed.
You've been forced to evolve,
so he wants to absorb you with
cursed energy manipulation.
It also seems Kenjaku has
connections to Sukuna,
which means he's been a sorcerer
for at least 1,000 years.
So then, why now?
Because myself,
the Star Plasma Vessel,
and the Six Eyes are all connected by
fate and intertwined with each other.
Twice in the past, Kenjaku was stopped
by the Sorcerer with the Six Eyes.
The second time, he was thorough.
He killed both the Star
Plasma Vessel and the
Bearer of the Six Eyes within
a month of their birth.
Despite that,
the Six Eyes and the Star Plasma Vessel
still appeared by the
day of my assimilation.
After that,
Kenjaku altered his strategy to
focus on sealing the Six Eyes
instead of killing him as he began
searching for the prison realm.
After all, there can't be two people
with the Six Eyes at the same time.
However, 12 years ago, something
unpredictable happened.
Toji Zenin intervened.
He was physically gifted
through a heavenly pact,
and he was unique among them for being
completely free from cursed energy.
Since his heavenly pact
placed him outside of fate,
he decided to destroy the
very fate that connected us.
Then, a young man with the power of
cursed spirit manipulation appeared.
Without even trying,
he now had all the necessary
pieces except for the Prison Realm.
But six years ago, the Prison Realm made
its way into Kenjaku's hands as well.
If Kenjaku has the Prison Realm, then
why is this Culling Game being hosted?
It's a warm-up before assimilation.
My assimilation with people other than
the Star Plasma Vessel is possible,
but at the moment there's a high probability
it will result in something incomplete.
The Culling Game uses the cursed energy
of the players and the boundaries formed
between the colonies in a ritual to send
this nation's people to the other side.
He probably plans to use that as a warm-up
to start their assimilation with me.
However, to establish that ritual,
Kenjaku should have been
forced to accept several pacts.
One of those pacts is that
Kenjaku is not allowed
to name himself the
Culling Game's Game Master.
Unfortunately, that's a
disadvantage to you as well,
because it means that killing
Kenjaku won't end the game.
Either all of the players must die,
or the players must all
refuse to participate and die.
The rules specifically
mention that nothing must
significantly hinder the
continuation of the Culling Game,
an insurance policy to prevent
the ritual from being stopped.
In that case... Yeah, right.
All of us need to participate
in the Culling Game,
and add a rule that creates
a way out of the game
for Sumiki and those
reluctant to participate.
We need to free Gojo-sensei
at the same time.
He could resolve this
all entirely on his own.
Uh, what do we do next?
First, please decide which
of you will stay behind.
I'll do it.
I'll stay.
Huh?
Yuji, you are absolutely going to need
the help of either Okotsu or that woman.
Noritoshi Kamo.
If Kenjaku comes, that's all the
more reason for me to guard Tengen.
I must do so because slaying him
would mean saving my younger brothers.
I'm still not finished
talking with Tengen just yet.
Does that sound okay, Okotsu? Yeah.
I don't want to be separated
from everyone anymore.
Thank you.
Now this.
This is the back of the prison realm.
If you plan to free Satoru
Gojo, you'll need it.
The back.
First, I've heard of it.
Like a back door.
That's right.
Before Kenjaku found it, the prison
realm was outside of my barriers.
Probably somewhere abroad.
I thought keeping this back sealed would.
obscure the presence of the
front, but it didn't work.
Satoru Gojo is also
sealed away within this
back gate. What?
Then let's open it and let him out!
No, the authority to open the gates rests
with the owner of the front, Kenjaku.
In order to break this one open,
you need either the inverted
spear of heaven that
can force the cancellation
of cursed techniques,
or something that can disrupt and cancel
out the effects of a cursed technique.
The black rope could
do it.
However, twelve years ago Satoru Gojo
either sealed the inverted spear of
heaven abroad or destroyed it.
Why would you do that sensei?
And last year the black rope was
also completely frayed by Gojo.
What was he thinking?
Reminds me of Miguel.
We went to Africa looking for
some more of that black rope.
So that's where you were.
Please tell me you found it.
Sorry, but it was a
complete waste of effort.
They said it's all gone.
Huh?
Is there another way? There is.
Among the players participating
in the upcoming Culling Game,
there's a sorcerer from 1,000
years ago who calls herself Angel.
Her curse technique can extinguish
any other curse technique.
Extinguish any curse technique?
Yes.
And Angel's curse technique also has the
power to open the back of the prison realm.
Can you tell us where she is right now?
She's in the colony on
the east side of Tokyo.
The barriers of the
culling game reject me.
I'm afraid I don't have any
more information than that.
Let's start going over things from there.
There are ten colonies across Japan.
They are linked together
by barriers designed to
ferry the country's people
over to the other side.
Crossing a river or other border.
acts that symbolize crossing
over to the afterlife.
These carry important meanings in sorcery.
Oh, it's like with Yasohachi Bridge.
The Jujutsu Society's barrier.
So is Hokkaido excluded?
It is.
That land is already established
as a vast sacred ground.
I guess that's the
challenging land for you.
Ferry them to the other side
may sound a bit dramatic,
but everyone in Japan was cursed in
preparation for the upcoming assimilation.
Tell me about this ritual.
How long will it take to complete?
Depends on the culling game.
My guess it's over in two months.
It is currently 9 a .m.
on the 9th of November.
Nine days since the players
awakened as sorcerers,
which happened October
City around midnight.
That gives us about 10 days and 15 hours
to go before Tsumiki is forced to play.
Tengen, you said before that people
would die if they refused to participate.
That's right.
They get stripped of their technique, huh?
I believe that rule also applies
to any sorcerers joining in later.
If that's the case, the stripping isn't
being done by idle transfiguration.
It's not a pact either, because
it says stripped, not prohibited.
So that probably means it'll be doing
something to the brain by force.
And it's better for the rules if
being stripped means death, too.
Otherwise, everyone would
refuse to participate.
It's just as Shoko anticipated.
But that also means there's no risk to
sorcerers without any
cursed technique like me.
And what'll happen to Panda?
Does he even have a brain?
About this rule,
what does it mean for the ordinary people
who are in the colony from the start?
It means anyone who wants will be
granted at least one chance to leave.
For real?
How awfully generous.
There are no stipulations in the rules
about leaving or entering colonies.
They were probably trying to stimulate
the culling game by giving players
a clear first-time goal of leaving
the colony with their lives intact.
In order to keep the players
inside for the duration.
The premise that players
entered of their own free will?
is extremely important.
Eno mentioned that thing about
adjusting the barrier strength.
Using fundamentally in a rule?
Why make it confusing?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Tengen, who is this Game Master?
Every individual player is
given a Shikigami called Kogane.
To be precise, Kogane
isn't the Game Master.
It's an interface.
It's best to think of the culling
game itself as the Game Master.
Okay, I got it.
So we can add, but we're not allowed
to eliminate any existing rules.
Maybe we'll be able to come up
with some kind of workaround.
How's that allowed?
Yeah, right.
It leans too heavily
on their own judgment.
No.
You should expect a fair decision
when it comes to all challenges.
They're already subjecting the
players to such stringent rules.
Jujutsu Sorcery would not allow them to
show more favoritism towards Kenjaku.
So then, does that mean I'll
be killing people again?
Maybe not.
I have a few ideas.
We've managed to organize
our information for now.
That just leaves the roles for each of us.
Yuki and Choso will remain here.
They'll guard Tengen.
Meanwhile, I need to return to the
Zenin house to get their cursed tools.
Right after Gojo was sealed,
the Kamo and Zenin clans
both took their cursed
tools out of Jujutsu
High's Forbidden Vault.
However, Megumi is now the
head of the Zenin clan.
Who?
I'll explain it to you later.
So we're free to rummage through
the Zenion's forbidden vault.
That.
Before that, Tengen.
I know what you want.
It's Juzo Kumio's Atelier.
Yes, thank you.
Once I'm finished, I'll look for Panda.
After that, I'll help deal
with the Culling Game.
And you, Yuta?
I'll enter a colony and
participate in the Culling Game.
The sooner, the better.
Before Sumiki and Fushiguro enter,
I want to know as much as I can.
Then I'll be thoroughly prepared.
Thank you.
It'll mean acting on my own once again.
However,
in order to prevent us from
clashing with each other,
and in case something does
happen to Sumiki out there,?
I'll avoid the nearby colonies.
We should be aware that the
colonies might cut off reception,
so I might be out of contact for a while.
If Sukuna appears and takes control
of me again, I need you to kill me.
Don't worry about that now.
It's gonna be fine.
If that happens, you
can have him kill you.
After I die.
Yeah, well, I'm trying
to avoid that situation.
Maki.
Right.
I want you two to meet up
with Kinji like we planned.
Kinji?
Kinji Hakari.
The third-year guy that got suspended.
We're shorthanded, so
it's all hands on deck.
Do whatever it takes to recruit him.
Is he strong at least?
He's a bit erratic, but if he gets into
it, he can be even stronger than I am.
That is impossible.
Joseph!
I want to thank you for all the help.
Don't die out there.
Are you really crying? Shh, shh.
Yeah.
Uh, thanks for coming.
Takaba!
How long are you going
to keep doing that crap?
Cut it out!
Ah, you're making me depressed.
The audience, too.
Yeah, I know.
How old are you now?
35 years old.
Just give it up already.
Our industry is full of late bloomers who
suddenly make it big for no good reason.
But not a single one.
Out of the blue suddenly
actually became funnier.
They were already funny people
waiting patiently to be discovered.
That ain't the case for you.
Look what happened to Tokyo.
No one's gonna think ill of you.
Go do something you're
actually suited for.
I always thought you were kind of funny.
You always made me laugh.
You mean it, Ken?
Both you and him have the wrong idea.
There are people who ain't
funny that still make it big.
Are they one-gag comics like me, though?
Absolutely not.
there are two types of comedians
that manage to stay big
comedians who are always funny
and comedians who can go ahead
and delude themselves into
believing they
are so
which type
are you well I'd like to think
I'm 50 50 but in Actuality,
it's probably a lot closer to 70-30.
50-50 or 70-30!
Thank you.
It's scary for you, too.
Na-zori na-kara nukau no-ho so!